# **Houba Vincent**

I am a fullstack developer with equal knowledge on the front and backend side.

I am a quick learner, I work with a lot of different thecnologies lanuages, library, frameworks.

I can Build static website, spa, mobile application, cli, create rest

api, work with sql and no-sql database deploy in cloud (aws)

My language of expertise are python (django, flask, aiohttp) and javascript (react, vue)

I am also a lisp hacker, emacs guru and a git ninja

# Experience

Front end engineering - (Robovision) - (June 2018 - April 2019) - (Belgium/Ghent)

- Create multiple tools to label images
- Build charts and metrics for quality of labeling
- Merge quasar (vue framework) version to more recent one
- Create multiple reusable component.
- Create an admin to create projects, users, group...
- Test components with cypress
- Python, Vue, Vuex, Vue-router, Quasar, Typescript, Es6, cypress, Docker

Full Stack Developer - (Factory) - (Aout 2017 - May 2018) - (Belgium/Liege)

#### P-heal

- Working on an iot device that calculate weight variations and blinking to help people take theirs medicaments
- Create a mobile application with react-native for the p-heal device
- Refactor the backend to aws with serverless

#### **Big Data Media**

- Create a recommendation engine for a broadcaster.
- Built a microservice to extract content from video.
- Test the recommendation engine with unitetest and behave.
- Searching for solution to improve the recommendation engine (tf/idf, elasticsearch).
- Create a cache system with redis to avoid collecting and fetching the same data.
- Collect data on users (time spended on article, time spend watching a video...) to rate articles and videos.
- Python, kafka, aiohttp, sql, behave, unittest, react, docker, redis, pyspark, pandas

Full Stack Developer - (Vesperia) - (June 2016 - Aout 2017) - (Luxembourg)

**Doctena** - Render their mail responsive with Ijml - Improve their javascript code base mainly angular and jquery - Resolve visual bugfix

**Logdirect** - Refactor front end code for different site, with jquery, gulp, css - Unittest made home framework with nodejs

atHome - Bulding static analyse tools with typescript (made home framework)

# **Education**

# Aug 2014-May 2015

# **Java cloud computing**; STE-Formations(Liege)

- Learning advanced design pattern in java
- Algorithm course on paper
- database analyse and creation
- Advanced sql with postgresql (view, trigger, creating function) psql
- Building a sudoku

### Aug 2012-May 2014

## Bac+2 Web developer; IPSF(Liege)

- Learning html, css, jquery, php, mysql, wordpress (first year)
- learning poo, symfony2, version control (second year)
- Building website for asbl in symfony2 (second year)
- Creating a site for lawfirm with python(django) (final)

## Skills

- Languages:
  - Python 5
  - Javascript (es6) 4
  - Typescript 3
  - Ruby 3
  - Bash 2
  - Node 2
  - Elisp 2
  - Elixir 2
  - Clojure 2
  - Php 1
  - Java 1
- Framework python:
  - Django 3
  - Flask 3
  - Nikola 2
  - Aiohttp 1
- Framework javascript:
  - Vue 4
  - Quasar 4
  - React 3
  - Redux 3
  - React native 3
  - Gatsby 3
  - Jquery 2

- Angular 2
  Integrations:
  Css 3
  Stylus 3
  Bulma 3
  Sass 2
  - Foundation 2
  - Bootstrap 2
  - Materialize 2
- Build tools:
  - Webapck 3
  - Brunch 2
  - Gulp 2
  - Grunt 2
- Servers:
  - Nginx 2
  - Apache 2
- Databases:
  - Postgresql 3
  - Mysql 2
  - Sqlite 2
  - Mongo 2
  - Redis 3
  - Dynamodb 3
- Tools:
  - Emacs 5
  - Git 4
  - Aws 3
  - Docker 3
  - Google cloud 2
  - Vagrant 2
  - Jira 2
  - Gitlab 3
  - Github 2
  - Bitbucket 2
  - Jenkins 2
- Os:
  - Ubuntu 3
  - Debian 3
  - Arch 3
  - Redhat 1

### Extra

- Languages:
  - French (native speaker)
  - English (excellent)

#### hobbies

- Webscraping, Machine learning, Game creation
- Reading
- Proxy http trafics from my webbrowser and try to understand what's going on

houbavince@gmail.com • +32499316385 • 29 years old

Quai de l'ourthe n 22 tilff - Liege, Belgium

Website: https://silly-mclean-010d02.netlify.com/cv